luxuryproperty.com 2011-12-08

# LuxuryProperty.com Privacy Policy — LUXURY PROPERTY

## _Last updated 8 July 2009_

**LuxuryProperty.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.**

NICHE technologies, Inc., d/b/a/ NICHE properties, (referred to herein as “the Company,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) provides the LuxuryProperty.com website (the “Website”) and related services to you (“User”), subject to the following Privacy Policy. (“Privacy Policy”).

This statement discloses our privacy practices. The purpose of this statement is to inform you:

  * What kinds of information we collect from users of the LuxuryProperty.com website and how such information is collected;
  * How the information is used by us;
  * Whether we disclose any user information to third parties;
  * How you can access, update or delete any information that we collect about you; and
  * The security procedures which we use to protect your personal information.

By using the Website, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time. If so, any such changes will be posted on this page. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on this website and does not apply to any other website operated by a member of LuxuryProperty.com.

LuxuryProperty.com is committed to meeting all of our obligations to our customers and website users to protect their data and only to collect, use, and disclose it for authorized purposes. LuxuryProperty.com is equally committed to abiding by all applicable domestic, national, and international privacy laws.

**HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**  
Generally, you can visit the Website without revealing any personal information. Like many Websites, our Web servers collect the Internet Protocol addresses, but not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. This information can measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, and other such statistics.

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve their experience at LuxuryProperty.com. LuxuryProperty.com collects personal information when you register with LuxuryProperty.com, when you use LuxuryProperty.com products or services, when you visit LuxuryProperty.com pages or the pages of certain LuxuryProperty.com partners. LuxuryProperty.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we may ask for information such as your name, contact information, physical address, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, preferences, and personal interests. Once you register with LuxuryProperty.com and sign-in to our services, you are not anonymous to LuxuryProperty.com.

LuxuryProperty.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. LuxuryProperty.com may ask you for credit card information to process your transactions with us, or to verify your identity or age.

LuxuryProperty.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page(s) and products you request. LuxuryProperty.com may also collect information from web beacons and shared objects.

If you choose to submit information when emailing a friend or real estate professional from our site, we will retain the information you provide to us so that we can send the requested information to the party of your choice. The e-mail we send on your behalf will allow that person to request that we remove his or her Personal Information from our system.

**HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**  
We collect, generate, retain and use your Personal Information for our own internal purposes in connection with the facilitation, recording and processing of any requests, communications, or interactions you may have with our Website. We also collect and store statistics and other information about you and your online activities on an aggregated, non-personally identifiable basis and in a manner that may allow us or our affiliated or related entities, third party content suppliers, or licensees to improve services to you.

Your Personal Information may also be used by us to provide you with information regarding our products and services. For example, we may use your e-mail address to send you special announcements and notifications of new real estate listings, services, or promotions that may be of interest to you.

**COOKIES**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow Websites to recognize you when you return and can keep track of information specific to you.

We use a programming tool that uses a temporary cookie to save persistent information on a per session basis. These temporary cookies are discarded as soon as you close your browser. This is a common way of saving persistent data in a Web application. We do not presently use cookies, temporary or permanent, to track users across multiple visits.

In addition, consistent with standard practices in the Internet industry, you may occasionally receive cookies from third parties to which you link from our Website. We do not control these third party cookies, and they are not subject to this Privacy Policy. If you prefer, you may set your browser to ask for your permission before your receive a cookie.

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**  
Information about our customers is important to our business, and we are not in the business of renting or selling it to others. We will not disclose the Personal Information you provide to us without your consent, except: (a) as required by law, (b) to our related and affiliated entities, (c) to our independent contractors who host and maintain our Web site and e-mail services, (d) to service providers or suppliers if the disclosure will enable that party to perform business, professional, or technical support for us, and (e) to third party associates who may have products or services of interest to you.

**RECEIVING PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS**  
If you opt-in to receive promotion materials by clicking on the appropriate button or checkbox provided on the screen at which you fill out on-line forms, we may send you information by e-mail or postal mail to the addresses you submit to us on the pages of our website. We may occasionally send you newsletters, and/or notify you of special promotions, new products or services, or other information that may interest you. You may also receive notifications of special promotions and/or new products or services from our third party associates.

If you previously indicated your consent to receiving promotional materials and no longer wish to receive them, you may opt out at any time by clicking the appropriate link in any received promotional item or contacting us at Support[at]LuxuryProperty.com and indicating such. Upon receipt of your request, we will take reasonable steps to deactivate your name from our promotional material lists.

**DATA SECURITY**  
Data security is critical to us and thus all Personal Information is held in a secured database. While it is impossible to guarantee the complete security of any computer system and the data contained therein, we maintain and implement robust security policies and procedures that combine with available technologies in accordance with prevailing industry standards, all of which are designed to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of your Personal Information.

**LINKS FROM OTHER WEBSITES**  
LuxuryProperty.com does not endorse and is not responsible for the information practices or privacy policies of websites operated by others that may be linked to our website. If you decide to access a third party’s website that may be linked to this website, you should consult that websites privacy policy.

**MEMBERS WEBSITES**  
Many members of LuxuryProperty.com have their own websites. We do not control or otherwise dictate the content or policies of such websites and do not require members to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Consequently, you should review the privacy policy of any member’s website you may visit before providing personal information on that website.

**NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 1998 (COPPA)**  
Use of the LuxuryProperty.com is not intended for minors under the age of 18 (“Minors”). Minors are not authorized by LuxuryProperty.com to use the LuxuryProperty.com even if Minors set up an Account or accept the terms of any agreement for LuxuryProperty.com. Parents or guardians may authorize Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 to use LuxuryProperty.com provided they assume all responsibility and legal liability for the conduct of such Minor including, without limitation, monitoring the Minors access and use of the LuxuryProperty.com LuxuryProperty.com. LuxuryProperty.com does not intentionally collect nor maintain any personally identifiable information from Minors. If you discover your Minor child has submitted his/her information to LuxuryProperty.com, you may request to have such information deleted from LuxuryProperty.com’s database by sending an e-mail request to Support[at]LuxuryProperty.com together with the e-mail address that was submitted by the Minor. Upon receiving the request, LuxuryProperty.com shall delete such information within twenty (20) business days. If LuxuryProperty.com learns that a Minor is using LuxuryProperty.com, LuxuryProperty.com will require verified parental or guardian consent, in accordance with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”).

**INFORMATION DISCLOSURE**  
LuxuryProperty.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies; and may be required to disclose information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
LuxuryProperty.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your LuxuryProperty.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**CONTACT LUXURYPROPERTY.COM**  
Please contact us to report violations or if you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy. You can reach us at Support[at]LuxuryProperty.com.

Customer Service/Privacy Policy/General Counsel LuxuryProperty.com  
340 S Lemon Ave #5353  
Los Angeles, CA 91789  
Phone: 1-877-589-7767
